

# **Professional Summary**

My name is Yurii. I'm an experienced marketing strategist & marketing funnel architect with 7 years of experience in the following niches: IT & Web Development, Aviation / Air Business, Digital Marketing, Coaching Programs &, Mentoring Programs & Online Courses, Architecture, Import/Export Business, Blockchain, Cryptocurrency.

Highly skilled and knowledgeable about leading the marketing department as a CMO, coordinating the marketing team, building a smart marketing strategy for business, fully developing the marketing funnel architecture (Strategy — Design — Website Development — Opt-in — CRM — Automation — Sales — Community Growth), and bringing clients directly to your business.

#### I'm experienced in:

- Digital Marketing Tools: InfusionSoft & Keap, Funnelytics, ClickFunnels, CoinZilla,
  DeadlineFunnels, Facebook Ads, Google Analytics, Google Ads, ManyChat;
- Business Integration & Automation Tools: Zapier, IFTTT, PlusThis, Parsey, Various Chatbots:
- Project Management Tools: Jira, TeamWork, Asana, Trello, Notion, Instagantt,
  Miro, TransNo, xMind, TryShift, AirTable, Monday.com, Google Calendar, Calendly,
  ClickUp, Acuity Scheduling, GSuite;
- UI/UX Design & Web Development: WordPress, Divi, Custom Coding Solutions;
- Learning Management Solutions: Kajabi, MasterMind, Udemy, AccessAlly, LearnDash, LifterLMS, Memberium;
- Data & File Management Tools: DocuSign, PandaDoc, Google Drive, Google Sheets, Google Docs, Google Presentations, Notion, Prezi, Vimeo;
- Communication Tools: Zoom, Loom, Slack, Discord, other messaging platforms;
- CRM Systems: InfusionSoft & Keap, Salesforce, HubSpot, ZohoCRM, Bitrix24, amoCRM, LeeLoo;
- All-in-One Solutions: ClickFunnels, Builderall;
- SaaS Administration Tools: Various Hosting Providers (WPEngine, BlueHost, HostGator, etc), WHM, WHMCS, Emails Web Server, Web Email Accounts;
- Security Tools: LastPass, 1Password, Yubi Keys.

My main focus: Blockchain & Cryptocurrency Industry. Fin-Tech Industry. Cybersecurity Industry.

# **Employment History**

#Crypto | Chief Marketing Officer, KamPay

2021 - 2021

#Crypto | Head of Marketing, Tycoon

2021 - 2021

#Crypto | Head of Marketing, Tranche Finance

2021 - 2021

#Crypto | Head of Growth, Blockswap Network

2021 - 2021

#Marketing | Marketing Funnel Architect, LSWW

#### **Details**

WA / Telegram +380930340994 yura.staryk@gmail.com

#### Skills

**Business Planning & Strategy** 

Agile Project Management

**Brand Representation** 

Critical thinking and problem solving

**Effective Time Management** 

**Communication Skills** 

**Creative Problem Solving** 

**Analytical Thinking Skills** 

Website Development & Sales Funnels Architecture

SaaS Setup & Administration

Business Intgr. & Automations

## **Hobbies**

I'm passionate about blockchain technology, cryptocurrency, cybersecurity, neuromarketing, coding, psychology, aikido, travelling and running.

#### Languages

**English** 

Ukrainian

Russian

Italian

Spanish

Polish

Indonesian

### #Aviation | Business Development Director, LAS Air Solutions

2019 - 2020

### #Aviation | Head of Marketing Department, LAS Air Solutions

2018 - 2019

## #WebDev | Web Developer, Shirley Parsons, London, United Kingdom

2016 - 2017

# Education

# Blockchain, Cryptocurrency, Coding

Codecademy, Programming Hub

## Cybersecurity, CEH, Python Programming

Skillbox, SkillFactory

### Finance, Management, Marketing, Psychology

Coursera, EDX, Udemy

#### **Master of Business Administration**

SEPTEMBER 2012 - MAY 2014

#### **Computer Science**

SEPTEMBER 2008 - JUNE 2012

# Courses

#### Cybersecurity, Skillbox

NOVEMBER 2021

## **CEH**, Skillfactory

NOVEMBER 2021

## Blockchain & Cryptocurrency, Programming Hub

DECEMBER 2020

## Python 3 Programming, Programming Hub

SEPTEMBER 2020

## **Fundamentals of Python Programming, Codecademy**

MARCH 2016

### IT Sales, First Lviv IT Sales School

JULY 2018

#### Neuro-Linguistic Programming (NLP), BDG People

JUNE 2017

# Internships

#### Web Developer / Project Manager, Casa per la Pace, Milan, Italy

SEPTEMBER 2015 - AUGUST 2016

# Links

LinkedIn - Yurii Staryk

Facebook - Yurii Staryk

Instagram - @YuriiStaryk

Twitter - @YuriiStaryk

Website - www.YuriiStaryk.com

# Counties I've Lived

# Bali, Indonesia

FEBRUARY 2020 - JUNE 2021

# Milan, Italy

AUGUST 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2016

# Lviv, Ukraine

JULY 2015

# Flexibility

# Remote

I have 10+ years of experience working remotely

## Relocation

I am ready to relocate and work together with the  $\ensuremath{\mathsf{Team}}$